computing.co.uk 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Incisive Media

**1\. INTRODUCTION**  
Incisive Business Media Limited and all companies within its Group[1] (“Incisive Media” or “We”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (“the Act”), the data controller is Incisive Business Media Limited of Haymarket House, 28-29 Haymarket, London SW1Y 4RX.

Our nominated representative for the purpose of the Act is Steven Henny.

**2\. INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**  
We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our sites, and which may be amended from time to time (“ **our sites** “). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment of your orders.
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

**3\. IP ADDRESSES**  
We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

**4\. COOKIES**  
For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on your browser or the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. Some of the cookies we use are essential for the site to operate. The cookies we use can be grouped into four separate categories:

  * Strictly necessary
  * Performance
  * Functionality
  * Targeting

Strictly Necessary  
‘Strictly Necessary’ cookies allow you to navigate the website and use essential features like secure areas and online registration. These cookies don’t gather any information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you’ve been on the internet.  
Since these cookies are essential in our being able to guarantee the performance of our website, should you disable them we won’t be able to ensure your security or predict how our website will perform during your visit.

Examples of strictly necessary cookies that we use include the following:

Incisive Cookies  
Kreatio_session  
logged_in

Performance  
This type of cookie collects information about how you use our website e.g. which pages you visit, and if you experience any errors. The information collected is anonymous and is only used to help us improve how our website works, gauge what interests our users and assess the effectiveness of advertising.  
Examples of performance cookies include:  
Incisive  
Kreatio_session  
WebSite_LatestJobSearchPage  
WebSite_LatestJobSearchCount  
WebSite_LatestJobSearchItems  
WebSite_LatestJobSearchListingPage  
WebSite_LatestJobSearchPageSize  
WebSite_LatestJobSearchOrder  
WebSite_LatestJobSearchID  
WebSite_LatestSearchRecruiterID  
WebSite_LatestSearchFirstJobID

Functionality  
This type of cookie remembers your preferences for tools found on our websites, so you don’t have to re-set them each time you visit. Some of them are managed by third parties. They may for instance determine whether you see the latest or oldest comments made in relation to an article first. Examples include:  
Incisive.grapeshot.co.uk  
uid  
Thenewswall.co.uk  
__cfduid  
__utma  
__utmb  
__utmc  
__utmz  
__utmv

Targeting  
These cookies are used to analyse what advertising might be most relevant to a user of the website based on the areas of the website that the user visits. Examples include:  
T.mookie1.com  
id  
mdata  
OAX  
YouTube  
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE  
PREF  
use_hitbox  
DoubleClick  
test_cookie  
id  
Please note that any advertisers featured on our site may also use cookies, over which we have no control.  
You block cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be to access all or parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon you visit our sites.  
Your first visit to any of our sites will generate a pop-up header alerting you to this privacy policy and will re-appear only in the event that you change your cookie settings from time to time.

Please also note that by clicking on the distinctive Ad Choices logo that appears in our sites you can obtain further information as to how cookies can be used or restricted in tailoring advertising relevant to you.

**5\. WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**  
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA working for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.  
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.  
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**6\. USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION**  
We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
  * To notify you about changes to our service.

We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post, email or telephone.

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box on the registration form or, alternatively, do not provide your consent to pass on those details when prompted.

**7\. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR DATA**  
We have put in place security procedures and technical and organisational measures to safeguard your personal information. Access to all internal data servers is limited to the specialist data protection personnel and is controlled via active directory authentication using defined policies to control password expiry and renewal.

**8\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**  
We may disclose your personal information to any member of our Group. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties under the following circumstances:

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * if Incisive Media or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our rights, to view our terms and conditions of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Incisive Media, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**9\. YOUR RIGHTS**  
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by ticking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#bbd2d5ddd4fbd2d5d8d2c8d2cdded6dedfd2da95d8d4d6 "Email info@incisivemedia.com").

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**10\. YOUR CONSENT**  
By submitting your personal information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. You may withdraw your consent at any time by writing to us either by email to Emma Scheck at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#20454d4d410e53434845434b60494e4349534956454d454449410e434f4d) or by post to her at New London House, 172 Drury Lane, London. WC2B 5QR.

**11\. ACCESS TO INFORMATION**  
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please send an email to Emma Scheck using the contact details set out in paragraph 10 above. 

We want to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. If any of the information that you have provided to us changes, for example if you change your email address or name, please let us know the correct details by writing to Emma Scheck as above. You may ask us, or we may ask you, to correct information you or we think is inaccurate, and you may also ask us to remove information which is inaccurate.

**12\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**  
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email.

**13\. HOW TO CONTACT US**  
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b6dfd8d0d9f6dfd8d5dfc5dfc0d3dbd3d2dfd798d5d9db "Email info@incisivemedia.com").

## REFERENCES AND NOTES

* * *
